Think about the last item of clothing you bought.
For me, it was my pants.
So let's look at what factors affected that decision.
Was it how you felt when you imagined yourself wearing it?
Was it your friends?
And what you thought they would think?
Was it because you've typically worn this style in the past?
Maybe your parents, siblings, or other family members had an influence on your choice.
Maybe you were trying to stay current.
We've all done it.
Did you see a commercial?
Maybe an ad or celebrity endorsement that helped convince you?
Was it because of a sale or a discount code that you had?
Or was it because of your own sense of values, style, and knowing what you really want?
In addition to all these factors, it's important to ask yourself when making any purchase,
can I afford this before spending the money?
Think of there are other things you need you rather spend your money on.
Listen, whether it's intentional or unintentional, all of these factors can influence the choices
and decisions that you make about spending money.
So here's a tip.
When you make decisions about spending money, take a moment to think about which factors
could be affecting your decision.
After all, sometimes we make good decisions like my pants.